Guide to the William Bird Ezra Pound Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Box 1, folder 41 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Box 1, folder 49 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Box 1, folder 54 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Box 2, folder 61 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Box 2, folder 68 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Box 2, folder 77 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Box 2, folder 78 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Box 2, folder 81 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Box 2, folder 82 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Box 2, folder 87 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Box 2, folder 88 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Box 2, folder 90 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Box 2, folder 92 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Box 3, folder 107 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Box 3, folder 125 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Box 3, folder 142 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Box 3, folder 144 (Box 5, Folder 181)